http://www.sunsweet.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to Main Content
Use this code for 10% off your first order:
10PCTOFF
Need Help?
10% off your first order
Use this code for 10% off your first order:
10PCTOFF
Privacy Policy and Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Sunsweet Growers, Inc. respects the privacy interests of our web site visitors. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information that we collect, the uses we make of that information, and how you can correct or request deletion of any personal identifying information you choose to give us.
Information We Collect
In general, Sunsweet Growers, Inc. does not collect personal identifying information from visitors to this web site unless such information is provided by the individual. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of Sunsweet Growers, Inc.'s internet servers, including the type of operating system and browser being used by the visitor. The information we collect allows us to make statistical analyses of the use of our site, to improve the content of our site, and to customize our site to better suit your needs.
Use Of Your Information
We may use aggregated information, which does not identify you personally, for advertising, marketing, promotional and other business purposes. Should you choose to provide personal identifying information, we may use and disclose that information in a number of ways related to your use of our site. We may use your personal identifying information in connection with sending you specific, targeted information that may be of interest to you. We may use your contact information, such as your e-mail address, to acknowledge your request for information or for other similar purposes. We will not sell our member contact list or provide your personal identifying information to any other person or entity in the ordinary course of our business, although we reserve the right to transfer such information in connection with a change in ownership of Sunsweet Growers, Inc. or its assets.
Cookies
We make use of "cookies," which are small sets of information stored onto your computer in connection with your use of our web site. We may use information gathered by cookies to measure certain traffic patterns on our web site or for similar purposes. A user does not need to have the cookie function of their browser turned on in order to use this web site. If you arrived at our site through a link from another site, it is also possible that these other sites may place a cookie or other identifier on your computer. We do not control and are not responsible for the use of cookies or other identifiers by anyone except Sunsweet Growers, Inc.
Corrections and Deletions
If you want to see the personal information we have collected about you from this site, or if you believe any information we have is incorrect and you wish to correct it, please write to us at the address given at the end of this Privacy Policy. If we change or delete information in response to your request, we will discontinue using it; however, some information may remain in backup records and may take time to be ultimately purged.
Security
While we take reasonable steps to protect your personal identifying information, given the nature of the Internet, we cannot ensure complete security and we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of any person or entity other than Sunsweet Growers, Inc. Although we take precautions against security breaches, hackers pose a threat to any Internet user, and the legal and regulatory status of matters on the Internet are uncertain both in the United States and abroad. For these reasons, we cannot guarantee that all of your personal identifying information will never be disclosed in ways you do not expect or which are not described in this Privacy Policy. We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, we obey court orders, and we honor subpoenas and other legal process. Your personal identifying information may be disclosed if we are compelled by law or legal process to disclose it. We may also disclose such information if we determine, in our sole discretion, that disclosure would be useful in connection with investigating possible noncompliance either with the law or with any policy of Sunsweet Growers, Inc.
Consent
Anyone under 18 should not send any information about themselves to us, including information like your name, address or e-mail address. Sunsweet Growers, Inc. does not knowingly collect personally identifying information from anyone under the age of 18. In the event that we learn that we have collected such information from an individual under 18 without parental consent, the information will be deleted from our database as soon as reasonably possible. Sunsweet Growers, Inc. reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to Sunsweet@casupport.com.
Terms and Conditions
Sunsweet Growers, Inc. is pleased to provide this web-site for your personal use. However, by using this site, you agree to the terms and conditions provided below.
Use of Site and Site Material
This site is provided for your personal noncommercial use. You may not copy material from this site for commercial use. You may copy material in limited quantities from this site for your personal noncommercial use provided that our copyright notice is affixed to the copied material. Sunsweet Growers, Inc. reserves the right to terminate at any time your permission to make personal copies of material from this site.
You are prohibited from using this site to post or transmit any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, or profane material or any material that could constitute or encourage unlawful conduct. Sunsweet Growers, Inc. may from time to time monitor or review material transmitted or posted using this site and reserves the right to delete any material the company deems inappropriate. Sunsweet Growers, Inc. is under no obligation to do so and assumes no responsibility or liability arising from any material transmitted or posted using this site.
Ownership of Intellectual Property
Sunsweet Growers, Inc. owns the copyright to this site. Notwithstanding any other term or condition in this agreement, Sunsweet Growers, Inc. retains ownership to the copyright in this site and all material from this site. Sunsweet Growers, Inc. owns the trademarks, service marks, and trade dress ("Trademarks") displayed on this site. Nothing on this site should be construed as a license to use the Trademarks. Your use of the Trademarks displayed on this site is strictly prohibited.
Disclaimer
Your use of this site and material from this site is at your own risk. Sunsweet Growers, Inc. strives to provide accurate and up-to-date material on this site. However, Sunsweet Growers, Inc. makes no warranties or representations as to the accuracy or timeliness of the material provided on this site. Sunsweet Growers, Inc. assumes no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions on this site.
Neither Sunsweet Growers, Inc., any of its agents, nor any other party involved in creating, producing, or delivering this site is liable for any direct, incidental, consequential, indirect, or punitive damages arising out of your access to, or use of, this site or any material from this site. Without limiting the foregoing, this site and the material provided on this site are provided "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NONINFRINGEMENT. Some jurisdictions may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so this statement may not apply to you. Sunsweet Growers, Inc. assumes no liability or responsibility for any damage to you, your computer, or your other property, due to your access to, use of, or downloading of this site or any materials provided on this site.
Jurisdiction
By visiting this site you agree that the laws of the State of California, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Conditions of Use and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Sunsweet Growers, Inc., and that the proper venue for resolution of any such dispute is Sutter County, California.
LinksSunsweet Growers, Inc. has not reviewed all of the sites linked to this site and is not responsible for any sites linked to this site. Your linking to any sites from this site is at your own risk. By linking to a site or permitting a link to this site, Sunsweet Growers, Inc. does not endorse the site operator or the content of the linked site.
Sunsweet Growers, Inc. may modify these terms and conditions at any time and without notice.
Get Feel Good Perks! Like 10% off your next order.
Coupons, newsletter, and more straight to your inbox.
Thank you!
